(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
そこに跪け！
Kneel before me!
吐いて捨てるような現実は
A reality that is spat out and discarded
一刀両断 叩き斬れ
Slash it through in a single stroke
終わりなき輪廻に迷いし孤狼よ
Oh, lonely wolf lost in the endless cycle of rebirth
漆黒の翼で誘おう
I shall invite you with jet-black wings
我ら エデンの星を統べる者
We are the rulers of the Star of Eden
秘密結社 HoloX!
Secret Society HoloX!
でござる！
...it is!
Kazama Iroha
Hello どうしようもないこの世界 どうして欲しい？
Hello, this helpless world, how do you want it to be?
Hakui Koyori
Blackout 終末告げる鐘が鳴る La Pa Pa Pa Pa Pa
Blackout, the bell announcing the end rings, La Pa Pa Pa Pa Pa
Sakamata Chloe
乱舞 手を踊らせ 嫉妬しようぜ 陰キャも陽キャも Sinners Oh
Wild dance, move your hands, let's feel jealous, introverts and extroverts alike, Sinners Oh
La+ Darknesss
気持ちいいことだけが全て 落ちていく 闇の底へ
Feeling good is all that matters, falling down to the bottom of the darkness
Takane Lui
Amai Mai Mai Melody 惚れろさあ どうぞ 手の鳴る方へ
Sweet, sweet, sweet melody, fall in love, now, this way to where the hands are clapping
もう逃げられない
There's no escape anymore
ほら 闇に染まれば
Look, if you're dyed in darkness...
世界を塗り替えろ 望めばくれてやろう 全て
Repaint the world, if you wish for it, I'll give you everything
常識 破り捨てろ
Tear up and throw away common sense
狂え 狂え いざ堕せ 極彩色の奈落まで
Go mad, go mad, now fall down to the richly colored abyss
ラッパッパーラッパ
Ra pa pa paa rappa
全てを喰らい尽くせ
Devour everything completely
ラッパッパーラッパ
Ra pa pa paa rappa
秘密を
The secrets...
教えてやろう
...I shall tell you
悪のカリスマ 導くぞ 民草
Charisma of evil, I shall lead you, my people
正義だか知らないし 鳴らしていいんじゃない？
I don't know about justice, isn't it fine to make some noise?
真面目に不真面目 テンションぶち上げで
Seriously unserious, with tension soaring
望み求め願い叶え 世界征服
Seeking desires, fulfilling wishes, world domination
La Pa Pa Pa De Tower 絶望しようぜ 退屈な世界へ Bye Bye
La Pa Pa Pa De Tower, let's despair, say bye-bye to this boring world
覚めることのない 夢を見せる ほら お眠りなさい
I'll show you a dream you'll never wake up from, now, go to sleep
もっと もっと 遠くへ 惚れろさあ どうぞ 行きたいんでしょう？
Further, even further, fall in love, now, come on, you want to go, don't you?
もうやめられない
I can't stop anymore
ほら 悪に染まれば
Look, if you're dyed in evil...
世界を塗り替えろ 望むもの与えよう 全て
Repaint the world, I'll give you what you desire, everything
ルールも書き換えろ
Rewrite the rules too
狂え 狂え 回し尽くせ 焼き尽くせ
Go mad, go mad, spin it all out, burn it all up
ラッパッパーラッパ
Ra pa pa paa rappa
全ての我が物へ
Everything shall be mine
ラッパッパーラッパ
Ra pa pa paa rappa
秘密を
The secrets...
教えてやろう
...I shall tell you
機は熟した！
The time is ripe!
狂気の宴の始まりだ！
The banquet of madness begins!
貴様ら、準備はいいか！
You scoundrels, are you ready!
オー！
Yeah!
刮目せよ！
Witness us!
手あげろ！ 手あげろ！
Hands up! Hands up!
イノハ！ イノハ！
Inoha! Inoha!
叫ぶでござる！
I'll shout!
こより！ こより！
Koyori! Koyori!
助手君！ 助手君！
Joshu-kun! Joshu-kun!
世界を手にするホロックス
HoloX, taking over the world
世界を変えてくホロックス
HoloX, changing the world
ルイねー！ ルイねー！
Lui-ne! Lui-ne!
もっと！ もっと！
More! More!
ラプラス！ ラプラス！
La+! La+!
最後は全員行くぞ！
Last, everyone let's go!
ホロックス！ ホロックス！
HoloX! HoloX!
世界を底にするホロックス
HoloX, making the world its base
世界を変えてくホロックス
HoloX, changing the world
世界をこの手にホロックス！
HoloX, the world in our hands!
心を解き放って
Release your heart
ほれ、どうぞ、お望み、身を任せて
Here, please, as you wish, entrust yourself
もう逃げられない
You can no longer escape
ほら、闇に染まれ
See, be dyed in darkness
世界も塗り替えろ
Repaint the world too
望めば呉れてやろう、すべて
If you wish, I shall give it to you, everything
常識、かなぐり捨てろ
Common sense, cast it aside
狂い、狂い倒せ、火をつけろ
Go mad, go completely mad, set it ablaze
ラッパッパッパッ
Ra-pa-pa-pa
すべてを食い尽くせ
Devour everything
ラッパッパッパッ
Ra-pa-pa-pa
秘密を教えてやろう
I'll tell you a secret
Wow oh...
この配信は、ご覧のスポンサーの提供でお送りします。
This stream is brought to you by the following sponsors.
えー、皆さん。本日は、ホロックスの２周年を祝う、記念配信にお集...
Um, everyone. Today, for this commemorative stream to celebrate HoloX's 2nd anniversary, you've gath—
お集まりいただき、ありがとうございます。
Thank you for gathering here today.
我々ホロックスは、２周年を迎えましたが、
We, HoloX, have reached our 2nd anniversary,
これまで...
and until now...
これまでと変わらず、いな！
We will continue as before, no!
これまで以上に世界征服のために、活動していくことを、
We will work towards world domination
more than ever before,
ここで改めて、宣言させていただきます。
which I would like to declare once again here.
そして、我が輩のお名前は、ラプラス・ダークネスです。
And my name is La+ Darknesss.
えー、３年目の抱負は、頑張ります。
Um, my resolution for the 3rd year is, I'll do my best.
では、２周年の抱負と自己紹介を、高嶺ルイから順番に一言ずつ頂きたいと思います。お願いします。
Now, I'd like to hear the 2nd anniversary resolutions and self-introductions from each member, starting with Takane Lui. Please.
はい。ホロックスの女幹部、高嶺ルイと申します。
Yes. I am Takane Lui, the female executive of HoloX.
えー、３年目の抱負は、歌を頑張るのと、
Um, my resolution for the 3rd year is to work hard on my singing,
えー、高嶺の「高」の字を間違えられずに、えー、ポストしてもらうことを目標に頑張りたいと思います。よろしくお願いいたします。
and I want to work towards the goal
of having people post my name without getting
えー、高嶺の「高」の字を間違えられずに、えー、ポストしてもらうことを目標に頑張りたいと思います。よろしくお願いいたします。
the 'Taka' in Takane wrong. Thank you very much.
はい！
Yes!
ホロックスの頭脳、博衣こよりです！
The brains of HoloX, Hakui Koyori!
３年目... えー、この２年目は２０００時間配信していたらしいです。
For the 3rd year... um, it seems I streamed for 2000 hours in this 2nd year.
だが、しかし、もっと配信だけじゃなく、歌やダンスなど、
However, not just streaming,
but singing, dancing, and more,
夢のソロライブに向かって、見てもらっていきたい。
I want people to see me working towards my dream solo live.
全て欲張って頑張っていきたいと思います。よろしくお願いします。
I want to be greedy and work hard at everything. Thank you!
はい。ホロックスの掃除屋、沙花叉クロヱです。
Yes. The cleaner of HoloX, Sakamata Chloe.
今年、あ、３年目の抱負は、もうちょっと勝ちたいです。
My resolution for this, ah, 3rd year is, I want to win a little more.
よろしくお願いします。
Thank you.
あ、ギャンブル？
Ah, gambling?
はい。次こそ勝ちます。
Yes. I'll win next time.
はい。ホロックスの用心棒、風真いろはでござる。
Yes. The bodyguard of HoloX, Kazama Iroha.
３年目の抱負は、今年はいっぱいオリジナルの楽曲を作りたいなーっていうのと、
My resolution for the 3rd year is that
I want to make lots of original songs this year,
今年こそ正社員になって、給料を上げてもらうことです。お願いします。
and this year I'll become a full-time employee and get a raise. Thank you.
えー、さてさて、我々ホロックスは、２周年を機にあるビッグプロジェクトを始動させようかと考えております。
Well, anyway, we HoloX are thinking of launching a big project to mark our 2nd anniversary.
はい。
Yes.
この度ホロックスは、人々に愛される世界征服を目標に掲げ、大型テーマパークをオープンすることになりました。
This time, HoloX has set a goal
of world domination loved by the people
この度ホロックスは、人々に愛される世界征服を目標に掲げ、大型テーマパークをオープンすることになりました。
and will be opening a large theme park.
それが、こちらになります。
And that is this.
バーチャルエデン holoXランド
Virtual Eden holoX Land
開園は、来年中を予定しておりますが、
Opening is scheduled for sometime next year,
本日はゲストの方々をご招待いたしまして、
Today, we have invited guests
一部アトラクションを先行体験いただこうと思っております。
to experience some of our attractions early.
というわけで、ここからはホロックスランドの...
And so, from here, the status of holoX Land's...
プレオープンの模様をお届けしていきます！
...pre-open will be presented!
アトラクションの体験会が終わったら、
Once the attraction trial session is over,
ホロックスのライブも開催します。
we'll also be holding a holoX live show.
これからもどうか...
From now on, please...
あ、こちらも皆さんどうかお見逃しなく。
Ah, everyone, please don't miss this one either.
噛みすぎですね。
I'm stumbling over my words too much.
じゃ、みんな行くぞー！
Okay, everyone, let's go!
モダンholoXランド
Modern holoX Land
ホイールシューターX
Wheel Shooter X
はい、開始しますよ。
Alright, starting now.
早く皆様、乗ってください。
Everyone, please board quickly.
えっ！？ 何、セクシーな声！？
Eh!? What's with that sexy voice!?
この声もしかして...
Could this voice be...
はい、乗って乗って。
Yes, get on, get on.
やめろ！
Stop it!
皆さん、グッドイブニング。
Good evening, everyone.
ホィールシューターXの...
I am the captain of Wheel Shooter X...
船長員、ホロクサー214号です。
Holoxer No. 214.
早くみんな、乗ってくださいね。
Everyone, please board quickly.
かわいいー！
So cute!
動いたー！
It moved!
大丈夫ですか？
Is everyone okay?
揺れる！
It's shaking!
ちょっと楽しいかも。
This might be fun.
一番楽しんでるぞ。
She's enjoying it the most!
はい、それでは改めて、このアトラクション「ホィールシューターX」について説明いたします。
Yes, now let me explain this attraction, 'Wheel Shooter X,' once again.
秘密結社holoX、新人構成員の皆様。
New recruits of the Secret Society holoX.
はーい！
Yes!
これからあなたたちには新人研修を行ってもらいます。
You will now undergo new recruit training.
研修と言っても、とってもシンプル。出題される試験問題にひたすら正解したらいーいだけです。
It's very simple training. You just have to correctly answer the test questions provided.
かんたーん！
Easy!
あの天高く伸びる打ち上げレーンの下にセットされた人は、私が出す問題に回答してください。
The person positioned under that launch lane extending high into the sky, please answer the question I ask.
なるほど、緊張する。
I see, I'm getting nervous.
正解できれば回答権は次の人へ。
If you answer correctly, the right to answer passes to the next person.
もし不正解なら、スリル満点「ホィールシュート」をご堪能ください。
If you answer incorrectly, please enjoy the thrilling 'Wheel Shoot.'
えー！？ ホィールシュートじゃない方がいいな。
Eh!? I'd rather not do the Wheel Shoot.
では皆様、新人研修頑張ってください。
Well then, everyone, good luck with your new recruit training.
頑張りまーす！
We'll do our best!
あの、話が勝手に進んでますけど、
Um, the conversation is moving along on its own, but...
新人研修って、団長別にholoX入ったわけじゃねーんですけど。
about this 'new recruit training,' I didn't exactly join holoX.
何を言っているんですか。
What are you talking about?
このホロクスランド、表向きはテーマパークですが、実は足を踏み入れたものを
This HoloX Land appears to be a theme park on the surface, but in reality, anyone who sets foot in it...
無理やり構成員へと教育する、ウルトラ新人研修場！
is forcibly trained as a member at the Ultra New Recruit Training Grounds!
略して、「USJ」！
Abbreviated as 'USJ'!
USJ! USJ!
そう、この場所においてはノエルさんも立派なホロクサーというわけですよ。
That's right, in this place, Noel-san is also a fine Holoxer.
いきなり話が進んでる。
The story is moving forward so suddenly.
まあ、もう一回乗ったからにはholoXの一員になるまで降ろしませんので。
Well, once you've boarded, we won't let you off until you've become a member of holoX.
構成員にはholoXへの愛と、愛と...
As a member, you'll need love for holoX, and love and...
愛と、ある... 愛を...
Love and, some... Love...
愛とある程度の学力が必要。
Love and a certain level of academic ability are required.
ルイさーん！
Lui-san!
回そう、回そう！
Spin it, spin it!
皆さん大丈夫ですか。
Is everyone okay?
まあholoXの皆様なら、新人向けの問題だから何なくクリアできると思いますけどね。
Well, if you're the members of holoX, since they're questions for newcomers, I'm sure you'll clear them without trouble.
holoXの問題でしょ？ 余裕、余裕。
They're holoX questions, right? Piece of cake.
大好き、大好き！
We love them!
それでは始めていきましょうか。
Well then, shall we get started?
次々出題するから、テンポよく回答してくださいね。
I'll be asking questions one after another, so please answer with a good rhythm.
レッツ、ホィール！
Let's Wheel!
よし。え、もう飛ばされるの？ 早くない？
Alright. Eh, am I being launched already? Isn't that fast?
私が、問題、来る？
Is my question coming?
大丈夫でござるか？
Are you okay?
結構ヤバい音してるでござるよ。
It's making a pretty bad sound.
止まるの不安なんですけど。
I'm worried it might stop.
さあ、次はノエルさんじゃないの？
Now, isn't Noel-san next?
打ち上げレーンの下にセットされた人は出題される試験問題に回答
The person set under the launch lane must answer the exam question.
問題
Question
ラプラス・ダークネスの一人称は？
What is Laplus Darkness's first-person pronoun?
問題。
Question.
ラプラス・ダークネスの一人称は何でしょうか？
What is Laplus Darkness's first-person pronoun?
吾輩！
Wagahai!
正解！
Correct!
holoXは何人？
How many people are in holoX?
こより様！
Koyori-sama!
問題
Question
はい！
Yes!
holoXは何人でしょう？
How many people are in holoX?
えっと、今はなんか6人になってそうだけど...
Well, right now it seems like there are six...
一応、5人！
But technically, five!
一応？！
Technically?!
え、でもね、入るから。入るから。
Wait, but I'm in it! I'm in it!
問題
Question
holoXは何年にデビューしました？
What year did holoX debut?
え？何年これ？
Eh? What year was it?
え、待って、何年だっけ？待って...
Wait, what year was it again? Hold on...
え、待って！逆算！
Wait! Counting back!
逆算しろ！
Count back!
あ、2021年！
Ah, 2021!
問題
Question
はい！
Yes!
holoXで初めて3Dお披露目配信をしたのは誰？
Who was the first in holoX to have a 3D debut stream?
誰？
Who?
あ、したの誰？はい、はい！
Ah, who was it? Yes, yes!
誰？え、この中で一番...
Who? Of everyone here...
風真いろは！
Kazama Iroha!
問題
Question
SS holoXの'SS'とは何の略？
What does the 'SS' in 'SS holoX' stand for?
あ、これ簡単！はい！
Ah, this is easy! Yes!
シークレット・シャレイ・ソサエティ！
Secret Society!
問題
Question
holoXが侵略予定の'エデンの星'とはどの星のこと？
What planet is 'Eden's Star', which holoX plans to invade?
はっ、これ言った！待って...
Ha, I said this! Wait...
歌にもなってる。我らエデンの星を統べる者...
It's in the song. We who rule Eden's Star...
地球！
Earth!
問題
Question
holoXの女幹部といえば誰のこと？
Speaking of holoX's female executive, who is it?
えー...
Uh...
え、誰だっけ？はい！
Eh, who was it? Yes!
鷹嶺ルイ！
Takane Lui!
問題
Question
風真いろはの刀の名前は？
What is the name of Kazama Iroha's katana?
これは簡単、チャキ丸でござる！
This is easy! Chakimaru de gozaru!
問題
Question
holoXで一番最後にデビューしたのは誰？
Who was the last to debut in holoX?
お、誰だっけ？
Oh, who was it?
えー、しゅ、しゅ...くー...
Uh, Sh- Sh- ...Kuu...
いろは！
Iroha!
問題
Question
沙花叉クロヱのファンネームは？
What is Sakamata Chloe's fan name?
わかりますよ！はい！
I know this! Yes!
飼育員！
Keepers (Shiikuin)!
問題
Question
holoXはデビュー何周年？
What anniversary is holoX's debut?
はい、はい！わかりますよ！
Yes, yes! I know!
holoXは2周年でござる！
HoloX is at its 2nd anniversary de gozaru!
問題
Question
ラプラス・ダークネスの角を除いた身長は？
What is La+ Darknesss's height excluding her horns?
え、今日な、え、どうしよう...待って、えっ...
Eh, today... eh, what should I do? Wait...
元々139cmだから、だから、えっと...
She was 139cm originally, so, uh...
え、113cmくらい！
Uh, about 113cm!
なな？！なんだよその予想！
Seven?! What kind of guess is that!
わかんだよ。普通に139だよ。
I knew it. It's normally 139.
正解
Correct
139cm
え、139？！角抜きで？！
Wait, 139?! Without the horns?!
それでは、クロヱ様...
And now, Chloe-sama...
クロヱ様には絶叫ギミックを味わっていただきましょう。
We'll have Chloe-sama experience the 'Screaming Gimmick'.
いきますよ、お仕置き！
Here we go, punishment time!
はい！あ、いいですよ。あ、あー、ありがとう。キモいでござる！
Yes! Ah, fine. Oh, oh, thank you. It's gross de gozaru!
さっさと飛ばされろ！
Just get launched already!
（叫び声）
(Screaming)
え、帰ってこないのか？
Eh, is she not coming back?
あ、あ、何これ？
Ah, ah, what is this?
お、なんだろう。すごいholoXのこと好きの気分になってきた...
Oh, what's this. I'm starting to feel like I really like holoX...
この仮面はですね、つけているとholoX愛がどんどん溢れてくる不思議なマスク。
This mask is a mysterious one that fills you with love for holoX as you wear it.
洗脳じゃん、それ！
That's brainwashing!
え、こわっ。洗脳じゃん。犯罪ですよ！
Eh, scary. It's brainwashing. That's a crime!
何だろう、このヘルメットかっこいい。
I don't know why, but this helmet is cool.
え、吾輩も欲しい。欲しい。
Eh, I want one too. I want it.
あ、このアトラクションの記念品なのでね。はい。クロヱ様しばらくこれつけといてください。
Ah, it's a commemorative gift for this attraction. So, Chloe-sama, please wear this for a while.
え、はずさないの？はずしたほうがいいよ。顔がちょっと隠れちゃいます。
Eh, you're not taking it off? You should. It hides your face a bit.
いやいやいや、まだまだありますよ。どんどん出さないと。皆、帰っちゃいますよ。
No, no, no, there's more. We have to keep going. Everyone will leave otherwise.
皆さんもっとWhirl Shooter X楽しみたいですよね？！
Everyone wants to enjoy Whirl Shooter X more, right?!
それでは皆さんいきましょう。レッツ・ホイール！
Alright everyone, let's go. Let's Wheel!
それはダサい。ダサいんだよな。
That's uncool. So uncool.
問題
Question
（プラットフォームが回転中）
(Platform is spinning)
吾輩は...吾輩は...あ、きたきた！
Is it me... me... Ah, here it comes!
問題
Question
風真いろはの語尾は？
What is Kazama Iroha's catchphrase/ending?
はい！わかった！ござる！
Yes! I got it! Go-zaru!
問題
Question
holoXの頭脳といえば誰のこと？
Speaking of holoX's brain, who is it?
はい！はい、はい、はい！こよりだよ！
Yes! Yes, yes, yes! It's Koyori!
問題
Question
朝こよは基本的に朝何時から配信している？
What time does Asa-Koyo basically start streaming?
これ、吾輩、吾輩わかる！こよりのさ、これ間違えていいと思ってる...
I, I know this! About Koyori's... I don't think you can get this wrong...
問題：朝こよは基本的に朝何時から配信している？
Question: What time does Asa-Koyo usually start streaming?
それでは...
And now...
キツい...
This is rough...
正解は...
The answer is...
正解：7時
Answer: 7 AM
知らなかったなー！
I didn't know that!
朝こよのことなんてどうでもいいんだ！
I don't care about Asa-Koyo!
かわいそうー！
How mean!
まさか7時だとは思わなかったですね...
I never thought it was at 7 AM...
寝起きだ...
She's just woken up...
じゃあ、しょうがない！
Then, it can't be helped!
ホロックス大好きになってもらいましょう！
Let's make you love holoX!
味わってください！
Please enjoy this!
行きますよ！
Here we go!
ホイールシュート！
Wheel Shoot!
いってらっしゃい！
Off you go!
飛んでった！
She flew away!
しばらく楽しんでおいで！
Go have fun for a while!
おおー！ラプちゃん！
Oh! Lapu-chan!
高い！めっちゃ...
It's high! So...
なんか普段とあんま変わらなくない？
Doesn't she look the same as usual?
あんま変わらないでござる。
I don't look much different.
なんか、洗脳足りてなくない？
Hey, isn't the brainwashing insufficient?
ホロックス大好き！めっちゃカッコいい！
I love holoX! It's so cool!
洗脳されてるのかよ！
Wait, she is brainwashed!
ただのキッズやめろ！
Stop being such a kid!
ここめっちゃカッコよくない？
Isn't this part super cool?
お前ら羨ましくないの？
Aren't you guys jealous?
欲しいでしょ？
You want it, right?
なんかカッコよく見えてきた！
It's starting to look cool!
じゃあ、ラプラス様置いといて、どんどんやっていきましょう！
Then, let's leave Laplus-sama aside and keep going!
はい、問題！
Alright, question!
問題：「音楽が好きで、よく音楽を聴いている。」これ誰の公式プロフィール？
Question: "Likes music and often listens to it." Whose official profile is this?
え、でも風真も音楽好きだもん！
Eh, but Kazama likes music too!
風真いろは！
Kazama Iroha!
お前バカか！
You idiot!
被りたいだけだろ、お前！
You just want to wear it, don't you?!
正解は...
The answer is...
正解：沙花叉クロヱ
Answer: Sakamata Chloe
えー、そうだったんだ。クロヱごめんね！
Ehh, so it was her. Chloe, I'm sorry!
それでは、いろは様、絶叫マシーンを味わっていただきましょう！
Now, Iroha-sama, please enjoy the screaming machine!
ホイールシュート！
Wheel Shoot!
いってらっしゃい！
Off you go!
花火みたいだったよ！
It was like fireworks!
ただいま、でござる！うわ、すごい！
I'm back! Whoa, amazing!
刀似合いそうや！
The sword would look good on you!
これでザクザクするでござる！
I'll slice and dice with this!
ホロックスを護れ！
Protect holoX!
ホロックス信者がどんどん増えていきますね！
The holoX believers are increasing one after another!
ノエルさん！何？
Noel-san! What?
何してるんすか？
What are you doing?
いや、普通にゲームを楽しんでる！
No, I'm just enjoying the game normally!
ノエルさん、ちょっと難しい問題とか！
Noel-san, maybe a harder question!
それでは、行きましょうか！
Now, shall we go?
レッツ、ホイール！
Let's Wheel!
問題：風真いろはのお供のたぬきの名前は？
Question: What is the name of Kazama Iroha's tanuki companion?
はい、問題です！
Alright, question!
ポコベ！
Pokobe!
正解！
Correct!
問題：こよりの配信を観ることで摂取できる栄養素はなに？
Question: What nutrient can you get from watching Koyori's streams?
こよりの配信を観ることで摂取できる栄養素はなに？
What nutrient can you get from watching Koyori's streams?
コヨリニウム！
Koyorium!
正解！
Correct!
問題！
Question!
ラプラス・ダークネス、キリン、カバ
Laplus Darknesss, a giraffe, a hippo.
おい！
Hey!
この中で角がないのは？
Which of these doesn't have horns?
えっちょ、これ関係なくない！？
Wait, isn't this unrelated!?
動物テストや
It's an animal test.
えっ難しくない？
Wait, isn't it hard?
ある程度の教養があればこれ...
If you have a certain level of education...
ラプラスはカバだと思うんですよね
I think Laplus is the hippo.
お前ふざけんな！
Don't mess with me!
キリンがあるもんだって！
Giraffes have them!
カバ！
Hippo!
問題！
Question!
風真いろはの弓の名前は？
What is the name of Kazama Iroha's bow?
弓！？弓って名前あんの！？
Bow!? Does the bow have a name!?
教養しているか、お、
Do you have the knowledge...
これ結構みんなわかんない、弓...
A lot of people don't know this, the bow...
あ、チャキ丸的な感じだよね、じゃあ
Ah, so it's like Chakimaru then.
うつきち
Utsukichi
あー不正解！
Ah, incorrect!
正解は本人からどうぞ
Let's hear the correct answer from the person herself.
キュウ助！
Kyusuke!
不正解のノエル様には、ホイールシュート味わっていただきましょう！
Incorrect! Noel-sama, please experience the Wheel Shoot!
ホイールシュート
Wheel Shoot
行ってきますって言ってたぞ、あの人
She just said "I'm off", that person.
楽しんでる？
Is she enjoying it?
ちゃんと楽しんでんじゃねえか
She's totally enjoying it, isn't she?
似合うんじゃないかな
Doesn't it suit her?
俺、ホロックス
I am holoX.
洗脳されてない？
Isn't she brainwashed?
大好き
I love it.
こえー、こえー、こえー
Scary, scary, scary.
怖い、怖い
Scary, scary.
いいなー
Nice...
元々付けてたかのような
It's as if she was always wearing it.
合ってる、合ってるよ
It fits, it fits.
やった、でもなんか嬉しくなってきた
Yay, I'm starting to feel happy somehow.
洗脳が効いてるぞ
The brainwashing is working.
はい、ノエル様が洗脳されたところで、続きいきましょう
Alright, now that Noel-sama is brainwashed, let's continue.
問題です。
Question.
ホロックスで4番目にデビューしたのは誰？
Who was the fourth to debut in holoX?
こよりかなー
Koyori, maybe?
大好きなあの1人でしょ
It's that one person you love, right?
沙花叉！
Sakamata!
はい、問題。
Okay, question.
ホロックス全員での初のオリジナル楽曲は？
What is the first original song by all of holoX?
これ間違えたら...
If you get this wrong...
アーティストだぞ、ルイ
You're an artist, Lui.
迷宮ラビリンス
Meikyuu Labyrinth
2曲目！2曲目！
The second song! The second song!
さっき歌ってたのに
We were just singing it.
正解は何でしたっけ？
What was the correct answer again?
「常夜リペイント」でした！
It was "Joyo Repaint"!
愛が足りない！
Not enough love!
これは回るしかない
There's no choice but to spin.
ホイールシュート！
Wheel Shoot!
本物や！
It's the real thing!
やっと止まった
Finally stopped.
とびっきりの笑顔
A dazzling smile.
かっこいいと思ってる
She thinks it's cool.
ポーズ決まってる
The pose is set.
一番似合ってる
It suits her best.
はい、それでは皆様、次で間違えたら最後でございます
Alright everyone, if you get the next one wrong, it's the last one.
YMDとは何の略？
What does YMD stand for?
はい、問題。
Okay, here's a question.
YMDとは何の略？
What does YMD stand for?
おまえ分かってる？ちょっとな、二つ正解...
Do you know? Wait, there are two correct answers...
いや、一個しかねーよ！
No, there's only one!
何をもって二つ...二つあんの？
What do you mean by two... There are two?
一個しかねーよ！
There's only one!
こより回したいからな。
Because I want to spin Koyori.
Yes, My Dark!
KHN 朝こよ内の何というコーナーの略？
KHN is an abbreviation for what corner in Asa-Koyo?
それでは問題。
Now, the question.
KHN 朝こよ内の何というコーナーの略？
KHN is an abbreviation for what corner in Asa-Koyo?
おっと、天から...天から声が聞こえてくる気がしない？
Oops, from the sky... Don't you feel like a voice is coming from above?
なんだっけ？
What was it again?
こよりずホットニュースであってます。
It's Koyori's Hot News.
なんか闇の取引してない？大丈夫これ？
Isn't there some shady deal going on? Is this okay?
こよりず・ホット・ニュース！
Koyori's Hot News!
「大事な所でミスをするポンコツ」これ誰の公式プロフィール？
'Clumsy person who makes mistakes at critical moments' Whose official profile is this?
はい、問題。
Okay, here's a question.
「大事な所でミスをするポンコツ」、これ誰の公式プロフィール？
'Clumsy person who makes mistakes at critical moments,' whose official profile is this?
私じゃないな。
It's not me.
沙花叉です！
It's Sakamata!
博衣こよりのファンネームは？
What is Hakui Koyori's fan name?
はい、問題。
Okay, here's a question.
博衣こよりのファンネームは？
What is Hakui Koyori's fan name?
もう、これ間違えたらやばい。
Man, it'll be bad if I get this wrong.
助手くん！
Joshu-kun!
“狸”なんて読む？
How do you read this kanji: “狸”?
はい、それでは問題です。
Okay, then, here's a question.
この漢字、なんて読む？
How do you read this kanji?
うわー、なんだろうな。
Whoa, I wonder what it is.
理系だからな、これは。
Since you're a science person.
圧倒的に理系だからね、多分。
You're overwhelmingly a science person, probably.
わい！
Y!
たぬき
Tanuki
はい、わかりました！
Yes, I've got it!
たぬき！
Tanuki!
はい、ホイールシューターX...
Okay, Wheel Shooter X...
楽しそう。
That looks fun.
やっぱ作ってる間に乗っときたいよね。
You really want to ride it while it's being made.
キャッチ！ちょっと長いんで。
Catch! It's a bit long.
お、おかえり！
Oh, welcome back!
あ、でもいい、いい、可愛い。
Ah, but it's good, good, cute.
可愛い！
Cute!
何持っても可愛いなこれ！
It looks cute no matter what she holds!
こより、こんなに嬉しいから...
Koyori is so happy that...
あのこしゅ大好き！
I love Joshu so much!
可愛い、大好きちゃん！
So cute, you're the best!
はい、ということで、全員ホロックスが大好きになったということで。
Well then, it seems everyone has come to love holoX.
以上で、本日のホイールシューターXは稼働終了となります。
With that, today's operation of Wheel Shooter X is concluded.
えー、そんなー！寂しいー！
Eh, really? That's sad!
では皆様、椅子のロックを外してあげますので、皆様降りてってください。
Now everyone, I'll unlock the seats, so please step off.
やっと、やっと出れたでござるな。
I finally, finally managed to get out.
え、かっこいい！なにこれ、かっこいい！
Whoa, cool! What's this? So cool!
最終的にマスクをつけているのは、我らホロックス！
The ones wearing the masks in the end are us, holoX!
イエーイ！全員だー！ホロックスプラス！ホロックス！
Yay! Everyone's here! holoX Plus! holoX!
恐怖で毒味してます、ホロックス守れ、守れ...
I'm checking for poison out of fear, protect holoX, protect...
おれキャラ変わってるんだけど...心失ったロボット...守る、守る...
My character has changed... A heartless robot... protect, protect...
そこまで下がんないでよ、大丈夫？
Don't back off that much, are you okay?
失ってるよ、ボインな俺は何かを。いいのかそれで。
I'm losing something, me and my bust. Is that okay?
かっこいい。
Cool.
かっこいいですか？
Is it cool?
やったー、仲間になりました！
Hooray, I've become an ally!
皆さんやってみて、どうでしたか？
How was it when you all tried it?
いやでも楽しかった、本当によかった。ちょっと怖かったけど。
Actually, it was fun, really good. A bit scary, though.
やったぜ、ありがとうね、呼んでくれて。
Nice, thank you for inviting me.
やったぜ、安心しました。
Alright, I'm relieved.
実はですね、まだ他のアトラクションにもゲストを招待してるから。
Actually, we've invited guests to other attractions too.
僕たちは移動しなきゃいけないんですけど。
So we have to move on.
あ、団長も行こうかな。新入構成員のノエルさんはホロックスランドまだまだここにいていいんで。
Ah, maybe Danchou should come too. New member Noel, you can stay here at holoX Land longer.
あ、色々楽しんでてて下さい。
Ah, please enjoy yourself.
楽しむって言っても一人じゃ...
Even if you say that, alone I'm...
あ、よし、行くぞお前ら！
Ah, alright, let's go guys!
バイバーイ！214もいますんで！
Bye-bye! 214 is here too!
二人きりね、楽しんでください！
Just the two of you, please enjoy!
え、じゃあ、乗ります？214さん。
Eh, well, shall we ride? 214-san.
ノエル様、一緒に乗ります？
Noel-sama, want to ride together?
え、乗ってくれるんすか？
Eh, you'll ride with me?
いいですよ。
Sure.
じゃあ、湿気して...寂しい...
Then, leave it... How lonely...
はい、それではね、ノエル様、乗っていただいて。
Yes, then, Noel-sama, please hop on.
早く！早く！画面変われ！
Hurry! Hurry! Change the screen!
爆発！ムカムカ角
Explosive! Angry Horns
爆発！ムカムカ角ー！
Explosive! Angry Horns!
イエーイ！
Yay!
盛り上がって、イエーイ！
Get hyped! Yay!
ロボ子先輩、アキ先輩もようこそホロックスランドへ！イエーイ！
Roboco-senpai, Aki-senpai,
welcome to HoloX Land! Yay!
えっ、な、なんか、大丈夫かこれ...
Wait, is... is everything okay here?
あれ、心配されてる？
Oh, are they worried about us?
いやいや違うんですよ。
No, no, that's not it.
これはですね、ホロックスランドの1つのゲームとして開発した、とっても楽しい遊びなのですよ。
This is a very fun game we developed
as one of HoloX Land's attractions!
なんだよそれ！角って我輩でしょう！
What's that? These horns belong to me!
えっ、どういうこと？
Wait, what do you mean?
この、いつもお邪魔で、ちょっと使い道のない角を...
We thought, these horns that are always
in the way and have no use...
言い過ぎだろ！
You're going too far!
...使って遊びができないかなということで、こよりが作りました！
...maybe we could use them for a game,
so Koyori made this!
え、すごーい！
Oh, amazing!
でも先輩、よかったじゃないですか、使い道できて。
But Senpai, isn't it great
you finally have a use for them?
ね、ようやく生えて生まれてきて良かったね。
Yeah, it was finally worth being born with them.
でも、なんか聞いたところによると、これって全部ホロックスの新人研修なんでしょ？
But from what I heard, this is all part of
HoloX's newcomer training, right?
僕別にホロックス入る気ないし。
I don't really have any intention
of joining HoloX, though.
研修という名では研修なんですけど...
It's called training, but...
今回なんと、成功するとご褒美があるんです！
This time, if you succeed,
there's a reward!
えー！ご褒美！
Whoa! A reward!
ご褒美あるんだったらやるぞ！めっちゃ盛り上がるじゃん！
If there's a reward, I'm in!
This is getting exciting!
なんなんだよこいつら元気すぎだろ。
What is with these two?
They're way too energetic.
でもさ、これってさ、何したらいいの？
But wait, what exactly do we have to do?
まあ、ちょっとなんかこれね、なんか見たことあるような記憶があったりなかったりみたいな感じなんだけど、ちょっと教えてほしいな。
I feel like I have some vague memory
of seeing something like this before...
Please tell us.
気になりますよね。それじゃあご説明させていただきましょう！
Curious, aren't you? Then let us explain!
お願いしまーす！
Please do!
爆発!ムカムカ脳
Explosion! Irritating Brain
えー、この「爆発！ムカムカ脳」。
Well, this 'Explosion! Irritating Brain'.
こちらは、えー、2人1組で挑戦をしてもらうゲームとなっております。
This is a game where you'll be
challenging it in pairs.
ラプラスの本来、ね、このためにある角を...
Using La+'s horns, which originally
exist for this very purpose...
...えー、後ろにあるこのコースにですね。
...on this course behind us.
2人でラプラスをかついで 角をフレームに当てることなくゴールせよ！
Carry La+ in pairs and reach the goal
without hitting the frame with her horns!
コースのフレームにぶつからないようにこう移動をさせて...
You have to move her so the horns
don't hit the frame of the course...
無事ゴールができればクリアとなります。
If you reach the goal safely, you clear it.
もし角がフレームにぶつかってしまった場合、なんと大爆発してしまいますね！
If the horns hit the frame,
they will cause a huge explosion!
大爆発！爆発！
A huge explosion! Explosion!
楽しみー！テンション上がってきた！ふざけんな！
Exciting! I'm getting hyped! No way!
これクリアしたらご褒美って言ってたけど、何がもらえるの？
You mentioned a reward if we clear it,
but what do we get?
なんとですね、このホロックスランド開園記念で...
Well, in commemoration of HoloX Land's opening...
クリア賞品 10億ヤマダラー (YMD)
Clear Reward: 1 Billion Yama-Dollars (YMD)
10億ヤマダラーをプレゼントいたします！
We will present you with
1 billion Yama-Dollars!
待って待って待って！ヤマダラー！？
Wait, wait, wait! Yama-Dollars!?
ヤマダラーって何これ？え、これメモ帳じゃなくて？
What are Yama-Dollars? Wait,
isn't this just a notepad?
これメモ帳よね？キッズが遊ぶものだよね？
This is a notepad, right?
Something for kids to play with?
ちょっと待て！我輩の顔印刷してあるけど！
Wait a minute! My face is printed on these!
ホロックスランドで使える！ちょっと待って、勝手に作られて勝手に悪口言われてるんだけど！
They're usable in HoloX Land!
Hold on, they made these without my permission,
and now they're badmouthing them!
いいじゃん、ビジュいいよ。可愛いよ。文字書いてあるよ。
It's fine, the visual is good.
They're cute. They have text on them.
どうですか？やりたくなってきましたか？
How about it? Do you want to do it now?
まあでもちょっとラプラスを爆発させたいって気持ちもあるし。
Well, I also kind of feel like
making La+ explode.
一緒にだよ、爆発は。
We'll explode together.
それでは早速、ロボ子とアキパイセンに準備していただきましょう！
Then, without further ado, Roboco and
Aki-paisen, please get ready!
ご準備お願いします！
Please prepare yourselves!
お願いします！イエーイ！爆発！爆発！
Please! Yay! Explosion! Explosion!
爆発！ムカムカ角 完全攻略できたら 10億YMD
Explosion! Irritating Horns.
Clear it and get 1 Billion YMD
ちょっと待て、どういう状況これ？おい！
Wait a minute, what is this situation? Hey!
さあ、お二方ご準備はできたでしょうか？
Now then, are you two ready?
よっこいしょー！ラプラスー！
Heave-ho! La+!
なんで持ってんだよ！離せよ！
Why are you holding me! Let me go!
おーすげー！実際に持ってみてどうですか？
Oh, amazing! How does it feel to actually hold her?
重いなんて言えない...重いなー！
I can't say she's heavy... but she's heavy!
あー、ロボ子さん助けてー！
Ah, Roboco-san, help me!
ムキッとして持ってしてもダメか。重かったわ。
Even lifting with all my strength... she was heavy.
持ちやすいですか？
Is she easy to carry?
持ちづらいよラプちゃん。
She's hard to carry, Lap-chan.
背も高くないから、背の高さがね。
She's not tall, so the height difference...
すごい、硬い！今日どうしたのラプちゃん？
Wow, she's stiff! What's wrong today, Lap-chan?
気づいたらなんか黒ずくめの集団が我輩をかつぎ出して...こうなりやがった！
Before I knew it, a group in black started
carrying me... and it ended up like this!
ということで、特に制限時間はございませんので、慎重に頑張っていただければと思います。
So, there is no time limit,
please take your time and do your best.
よし、ラプ、お前動くなよ。
Alright, Lap, don't you move.
いや動けないんだって。動けたら逃げてるよ！
I told you I can't move!
If I could, I'd be running away!
それでは「爆発！ムカムカ脳」、スタート！
Then, 'Explosion! Irritating Brain', START!
OK！はい、いくよー。
OK! Here we go.
グルグルしちゃいますよー。イエーイ！
It's gonna be spinning. Yay!
まだ許してないから！おいおいおい、いい感じ！
I haven't forgiven you yet!
Hey, hey, looking good!
慎重に、ゆっくり！結構うまいじゃん！
Carefully, slowly! They're actually pretty good!
あー、ちょっと待て！ふざけんなよマジで！
Ah, wait a minute! Don't mess around, seriously!
ちょ、これ顔に当たる、顔に当たるってこれ！
Wait, it's gonna hit my face,
it's gonna hit my face!
顔はいいだろ、どういうこと？当たり判定角しかないの？
The face is fine, what? Is the hit
detection only on the horns?
あー！当たっちゃってるって！シンプルに痛いだろ！
Ah! It's hitting! That simply hurts!
次！せーの、おい！
Next! One, two, hey!
いけいけいけいけ！
Go, go, go, go!
わー！ちょっと待って待って！
Whoa! Wait, wait, wait!
おーおーおー、大丈夫？いいのそれ？
Whoa, whoa, whoa, is that okay? Is that okay?
うわー！刺さってる刺さってる！
Whoa! It's sticking! It's sticking in!
あ、ちょっと待って！あ、刺さってる！
Ah, wait a second! Ah, it's stuck!
あれ？焦げ臭い…なんで？なんか臭いんだけど。
Huh? It smells burnt... why? Something smells.
いや、お前もだよ！お前らも爆発してんだよ！
No, you too! You guys also exploded!
でも強かった。
But it was strong.
なんでこの状況で笑っているの！？
Why are you laughing in this situation!?
ふざけんな！
Don't mess with me!
なんでやり切ったみたいな顔…
Why that "I did it" look on your faces?
やり切ったわ。
I totally did it.
全然良くない？
Wasn't it totally fine?
え？もうやり切った。
Eh? I've already done my part.
あれ？さすがです先輩方。そうだよね。
Eh? As expected of you seniors. Right?
やり切ったやり切った。
Did it, did it.
違う違う違う！自分の顔見てみろよ！
No, no, no! Look at your own faces!
え？何これ？めっちゃ真っ黒なんだけど！
Eh? What's this? It's totally black!
あ、なんか焦げ臭いか、ちょっと。
Ah, it smells a bit burnt, doesn't it?
焦げ臭いどころじゃねえよ！普通に事故ってたぞ！
It's more than just smelling burnt! It was a total accident!
あまりにも強すぎる。さすがにこれは失敗かな？
It's way too strong. This is probably a failure.
え、失敗かな？
Eh, a failure?
そりゃそうだろ。ラプラス、じっとしておけよ！
Obviously! La+, stay still!
お前、ラプラス動くのか。
You... so La+ actually moves.
で、やってみてどうでしたか？
So, how was it trying it out?
いや、思ってるより難しいかもしんない。
Actually, it might be harder than it looks.
そう、角がね、デカい。邪魔。
Yeah, those horns are huge. They're in the way.
お気づきになられましたか？
Did you just notice that?
気づいちゃった。あれ大変だわ。
I noticed! That's a lot of work.
てめぇらおもちゃにしやがって許さねぇからな絶対に！
I'll never forgive you guys for treating me like a toy!
なんか言ってるよ。
She's saying something.
やばい揺らすな、揺らすな！やめろ！
Crap, don't shake her! Stop it!
じゃあ次、ちょっと交代してみましょうか。
Well then, let's try switching next.
まだやるのこれ？
Are we still doing this?
じゃあクロヱといろは行きましょう。
Okay, let's go with Chloe and Iroha.
一番不安一番不安！お手本を見せてあげてくださいよ。
I'm so nervous! Please show them how it's done.
先輩方にね。
For the seniors.
ちょ、やめて！やめてよ！
Hey, stop! Stop it!
よいしょ。いろはちゃん待って。
Heave-ho. Iroha-chan, wait.
私を見殺しにするんですか？
Are you going to let me die?
爆発！ムカムカ角 完全攻略できたら10億YMD
Explosion! Mukamuka Horns. Clear it perfectly for 10 Billion YMD.
風真いろは 沙花叉クロヱ
Kazama Iroha & Sakamata Chloe
クロヱ、いろは、準備は大丈夫ですか？自信はどうでしょう？
Chloe, Iroha, are you ready? How's your confidence?
なんか爆発したら巻き込まれるって聞いたんでマジで嫌なんですけど…
I heard if it explodes I'll be caught in it, so I really hate this...
あの、ちょっと爆発させてみたいです。
But, I kind of want to see it explode.
好奇心が勝っているようで。
Seems your curiosity is winning out.
ま、なんとかなるしよ。ね、なんとかなるさ。
Well, it'll work out somehow. Right, it'll be fine.
じゃあね、ちょっとお手本を見せてもらいましょう。
Then, let's have you show us a good example.
それでは爆発ムカムカ角、スタート！
Now then, Explosion Mukamuka Horns, START!
ちょっと待っていろはちゃん、命かかってる！
Wait a minute Iroha-chan, life is on the line!
いろはちゃんの命が…
Iroha-chan's life is...
ラプラスはどうでもいいけど。ごめんたすかり。
I don't care about La+, but... sorry, thanks.
お前ら本当にどうでもいいみたいだからな！
You guys really don't seem to care about me at all!
あるかな、順調、いい感じいい感じ。
Is it there? Smooth sailing, looking good.
あ、大丈夫これ。あー、怖い怖い。
Ah, is this okay? Ah, scary, scary.
これどう？これどう？あ、角判定判定…
How's this? Is the horn being judged...?
行ける、行ける！怖い、顔に近い！
I can do it! Scary, it's so close to the face!
やめて！待っていろはちゃん、待って待って待って！
Stop! Wait Iroha-chan, wait wait wait wait!
ここで考え直そう。一回深呼吸をしろ。
Let's rethink here. Take a deep breath once.
うちらの将来のプラン。せーの。
Our future plans. Ready, and...
待て、どこでいく？これの次で行こう。
Wait, when do we go? Let's go after this one.
せーの、わー！
Ready, and... Whoa!
はい、おーい。残念ながら…いやいや、やり切ったじゃないんだよ。
Okay, hey. Unfortunately... no no, it's not "we did it."
ほらこうやって真っ黒になったよ。
Look, we've turned black like this.
やったね！
We did it!
はい、残念ながら失敗となります。
Yes, unfortunately it's a failure.
え？残念とかじゃねーから！
Eh? It's not just "unfortunate"!
お前の角がでっけーからでござる！
It's because your horns are so big!
もっと慎重にやれよ下手くそ。
Do it more carefully, you unskilled lot.
でもまあラプラスだし。角デカいでござる。
Well, it is La+... her horns are huge.
ねぇ、角デカすぎる！あ、それさっきも聞いた。削ってくれ。頼む。
Seriously, the horns are too big! I heard that earlier! Shave them down, please!
次、ちょっとラプラスから愛されているこよりと、信頼を置かれているルイでやりましょうか。
Next, let's have Koyori, who is loved by La+, and Lui, who is trusted by her, do it.
いや、ここは頭脳を見せていきましょうよ。
No, let's show our brains here.
エリートにやって…
Do it like an elite...
おぎゃって言っていいんだよ。
It's okay to cry like a baby.
は、いや、ちょっとこの状況はさすがに喜べない…
Wait, I can't exactly enjoy this situation...
爆発！ムカムカ角 完全攻略できたら10億YMD
Explosion! Mukamuka Horns. Clear it perfectly for 10 Billion YMD.
鷹嶺ルイ 博衣こより
Takane Lui & Hakui Koyori
え、ちょっと本当に信じてるからね。
Wait, I'm really believing in you.
何を？
In what?
お前らをだよ！お前らがクリアすることだよ！
In you guys! That you guys will clear it!
頑張ります！
We'll do our best!
山田ルイ54世の絆、頑張ります。
The Yamada-Lui 54th generation bond, we'll do our best.
（歓声）
(Cheering)
一番不安。
Most anxious.
じゃあ、準備できました？
Alright, are you ready?
OK!
はい、それでは、爆発ムカムカズのん、スタート！
Alright then, Explosive Mukamukazunon, start!
（歓声）
(Cheering)
早くこの地獄から解放してくれ。
Free me from this hell quickly.
危ない危ない。
Watch out, watch out.
（指示や歓声）
(Instructions and cheering)
うまいかも。
You're good at this.
（指示や歓声）
(Instructions and cheering)
これ君ら、さっきのとは大違いだ。絆だ。
You guys are totally different from before. It's a bond.
流石にここは速いよ。
As expected, we're fast here.
おお、うまい！丁寧！
Oh, nice! So careful!
ラプラスに対して、なんかちょっと安心感を感じる。
I feel a sense of security regarding La+.
母性がね、愛があるね。
Motherly love, right? There's love.
危ない危ない！ちょっと怖い怖い怖い！
Watch out, watch out! A bit scary, scary, scary!
せーの、行け行け行け！
Ready, go go go!
（歓声）
(Cheering)
痛い痛い痛い！
Ow ow ow!
すごいいいよ、これいいぞ！
Looking great, this is good!
もうクリアでいいよ！
It's fine to clear it now!
おおー、行け行け行け！
Ooh, go go go!
（爆発音）あーー！
(Explosion) Aaaah!
お前ら、何やってくれてんだよ！
What the hell did you guys do?!
めちゃくちゃ上手かったじゃない！
We were so good, weren't we?!
めちゃくちゃ上手かった！
We were so good!
どうでしたか？
How was it?
どうだった、どうだった？どんな番組？
How was it, how was it? What kind of show is this?
ああ、もう、簡単だったね。
Ah, well, it was easy.
おおー、余裕だった。
Oh, it was a breeze.
恥ずかしくないんかお前ら。
Aren't you guys ashamed?
全員こうなるんだね。面白い。
Everyone ends up like this. How funny.
ふざけんなよ！くせーな！
Don't mess with me! It stinks!
途中までね、焦げなかったし、凄かったよ。
You didn't get scorched until the halfway point, it was great.
我々は成功しましたから。
Because we succeeded.
おめでとう！
Congratulations!
イエーイ！これが絆ってことよ。
Yay! This is what you call a bond.
レベル低すぎだろ。
The level is too low.
はい、ということで、あ、ラプラスさん、体戻ったね。
Alright then, ah, La+-san, your body is back to normal.
ホントだよ、ふざけんなよ。
Seriously, don't mess with me.
また黒ずくめの人たちに戻されたけど。
Sent back by the people in black again.
さっきのも良かったけどね。可愛かったよ。
The previous one was good too though. It was cute.
可愛かったわ。
It was cute.
まあやってみたわけですけど、どうでしたか？ロボ子先輩、アキ先輩。
Well, we tried it, but how was it? Roboco-senpai, Aki-senpai.
でも、ラプラス持つのちょっと楽しかったよね。
But, holding La+ was a bit fun, wasn't it?
そう、思った以上に楽しくて、今もう一回やりたいもん。
Yeah, it was more fun than I thought, I want to do it again right now.
本当に！？
Really!?
もう一回カチカチになって。
Become stiff one more time.
次は爆発しないよ。
Next time it won't explode.
もう何も、誰も信じられない。
I can't believe anything, anyone anymore.
アキロゼ先輩は信用ならんぞ、あれは。
Akirose-senpai can't be trusted, that one.
私は一人で生きていく。
I will live alone.
なんか好き勝手やれるって楽しいんだなーって思いました。
I thought, it's fun to be able to do whatever you want.
わかるわかる。というか、日頃の恨みというか。
I get it, I get it. Or rather, a daily grudge or something.
やった！うるせー、馬鹿共が。
Yay! Shut up, you idiots.
というわけでですね、あの、ホロメンの皆様！
And so, um, everyone in Hololive!
こちらのムカムカズのんがクリアできれば、holoX大総帥の席をご用意しております！
If you can clear this Mukamukazunon, we have prepared the seat of the holoX Great Leader!
（歓声）大総帥になれる！
(Cheering) You can become the Great Leader!
はい、自信ある人はね。
Yes, those who are confident.
そう、練習しに来て。
Yeah, come and practice.
お越しください！holoXランドにお越しください！
Please come! Please come to holoX Land!
というわけで、次なる挑戦者は、誰だ！
And so, the next challenger is... who!?
誰だー！来るなー！
Who is it?! Don't come!
やめちまえ！
Just quit it!
誠に遺憾です。
It is truly regrettable.
（遺憾です）
(It's regrettable)
本当に遺憾です。
It's truly regrettable.
楽しかったね。
It was fun, wasn't it?
お前らだけだよ楽しかったの！ふざけんなよ！
You guys were the only ones who had fun! Don't mess with me!
いやー、たまには役に立つツノでござるな。
Well, it's a horn that's useful once in a while.
さー、でもですね、一応この後は...
Now then, but, for now, after this...
貴様らお待ちかねの、ライブ！ライブ！
What you've all been waiting for, Live! Live!
チャンネルはそのままで。
Don't change the channel.
があるんですが、その前にここで我輩たちに関するお知らせが、もういっぱい、いっぱい、いっぱいあるんで！
But before that, there are lots and lots and lots of announcements about us here!
心して聞くように。はい、じゃあ、ルイ、お願いします。
Listen carefully. Alright then, Lui, please.
え、あ、私？はい、じゃあまず...
Eh, ah, me? Alright, then first...
holoXの活動2周年記念グッズの紹介をいたします！
I will introduce the holoX 2nd Anniversary merchandise!
（歓声）今回もあるぞ！
(Cheering) We have them this time too!
はい、ということで、こちら。こっちこっちこっち！
Alright, so here it is. This way, this way, this way!
はい、ということで、このイラストめちゃくちゃカッコよくないですか？
Alright, so, isn't this illustration incredibly cool?
先日ね、あの紹介した、ヘッドセットをつけた描き下ろしイラストになっております。
It's a newly drawn illustration wearing the headset we introduced the other day.
黒井ススム先生に、描いていただきました。ありがとうございます。
It was drawn by Kuroi Susumu-sensei. Thank you very much.
よいしょ、お尻触られた。じゃあグッズも早速見ていきましょう。
Heave-ho, my butt was touched. Let's take a look at the goods right away.
こちらに座っちゃった。まずはこちら、チェンジングキーホルダー。
I ended up sitting here. First of all, the Changing Keychain.
角度を変えると、ヘッドセットから、マスクに変身するという、かっこいいキーホルダーになっております。
It's a cool keychain that transforms from a headset to a mask when you change the angle.
え、すごい！そうそう、これこれ。反射のやつだ。
Whoa, amazing! Yes, yes, this one. It's the reflective kind.
修学旅行で買うやつみたい！めっちゃ可愛い！
Like the ones you buy on school trips! So cute!
（歓声）めっちゃ可愛い！
(Cheering) So cute!
はい、欲しい。欲しいでしょ？
Yes, I want it. You want it, right?
っと、いろはの分もありますよ。こちら。
And we have Iroha's version too. This one.
私の分もあります。
And mine is here too.
作ってよかったねー！
I'm glad they were made!
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
こちらは、それぞれ単体で販売されますので、
These will be sold individually, so...
推しのキーホルダーを手に取っていただければと思います。
I hope you'll pick up your favorite member's key holder.
もちろん、5人全員集めていただくのも大歓迎です！
Of course, collecting all five of us is also very welcome!
欲しい！欲しい！欲しい！
I want it! I want it! I want it!
そしてそして、こちらもご覧ください。どうぞ！
And next, please look at this. Here you go!
はい！5人揃ったイラストのラバーマットが登場です！
Yes! A rubber mat with an illustration of all five of us is here!
おー！可愛い！かっこいい！
Oh! So cute! Cool!
お仕事や、お勉強、ゲームをする際のデスクマットにもお使いいただけます。
You can use it as a desk mat for work, study, or gaming.
何やってんだよ。ほら、このラバーマット、かっこいいっしょ？
What are you doing? Look, this rubber mat is cool, right?
欲しかったよね、きっと。
You probably wanted it.
そして、お次は実に我々っぽいグッズですよ。こちら！
And next is a piece of merch that's very "us". This!
なんと！holoXのアタッシュケースが登場です！
No way! The holoX attache case is here!
ね？秘密結社っぽいでしょ？
See? It looks like something from a secret society, right?
外側にはholoXのロゴ、
On the outside is the holoX logo,
そして中にはアジトの鍵が入っております！
And inside, there's a key to the hideout!
え！？いいの！？セキュリティー！セキュリティー！
What!? Is that okay!? Security! Security!
嘘だろ！？でも、来れるもんなら来てみな！
No way!? But, come if you think you can!
止めろ！特定されたら入られちゃう！
Stop it! If it's located, people will break in!
中のクッションは取り外しができますので、イベントなんかでも使えるんじゃないかなと思います。
The cushion inside is removable, so I think it'll be useful for events and such.
楽しみ！
I'm looking forward to it!
はい、そして最後はこちらです。
Yes, and finally, here is this.
デビュー記念でも販売しましたピンバッジ、皆さん覚えておりますでしょうか。
The pin badge we sold for our debut, does everyone remember it?
2周年記念バージョンが登場しております！
A 2nd-anniversary version is now available!
なので、デビュー記念のものと合わせてコンプリートしていただくのと、
So, please complete your collection with the debut one...
あと途中からholoXファンになった方に関しては...大丈夫ですか？見切れてる人もいますけど。
And for those who became holoX fans midway through... Are you okay? Some of you are being cut off.
いなくなってるよ！ぜひぜひこの機会に買っていただければなと思います。
You're disappearing! Anyway, please take this chance to buy them.
ただいま紹介した2周年記念グッズはこの後22時より販売開始になります。
The 2nd-anniversary goods I just introduced will go on sale starting at 10 PM today.
気になった方はぜひチェックしてみてくださいね。
If you're interested, please check them out.
お願いしまーす！
Please do!
じゃあ、次のお知らせを博衣こよりさん、よろしくお願いします。
Alright, Hakui Koyori-san, please give us the next announcement.
はい！今回なんと！こよの、
Yes! This time, believe it or not...
大好きなあのイベントが開催されることになりました！
That event I love so much is going to be held!
なんですか？
What is it?
まずはこちらの映像をご覧ください。ドン！
First, please watch this video. Bam!
これはキミたちへの挑戦状だ。
This is a challenge to all of you.
ぼくたち秘密結社holoXが作った極上のラビリンス！
A supreme labyrinth created by us, Secret Society holoX!
たっくさんの謎が仕掛けられたラビリンスの奥に――
Deep inside the labyrinth, where many riddles are hidden...
キミはたどり着けるかな？
Will you be able to reach it?
必要なのは知恵とヒラメキと風真たちへの忠誠心！
What you need is wisdom, inspiration, and loyalty to the Kazama Clan!
貴様らの挑戦を待っているぞ！！
I'll be waiting for your challenge!!
Yes, My Dark!!
強制的だったからねー。抗えない。
It was mandatory, after all. Resistance is futile.
ということで、holoXの謎解きイベントが開催決定しましたー！
So, the holoX riddle-solving event has been officially decided!
その名も、秘密結社holoXからの招待状、迷宮なラビリンスからの脱出 in 渋谷！
The name is: "Invitation from Secret Society holoX: Escape from the Labyrinth in Shibuya"!
holoXのオリジナル楽曲「迷宮なラビリンス」の世界観の中で行われる謎解き脱出ゲームになっております。
It's a riddle-solving escape game set in the world of holoX's original song, "Dramatic Labyrinth".
こちらの謎解きイベントは一週間後の12月9日から、渋谷BEAMの4階で開催いたします！
This riddle-solving event will be held starting in a week, from December 9th, at Shibuya BEAM 4F!
なんとイベント参加チケットは本日22時から、先着予約販売開始なので要チェックです！
Unbelievably, event tickets go on sale tonight at 10 PM on a first-come, first-served basis, so check it out!
詳しくは特設サイトをチェックしてみてください。
For details, please check the special website.
さらに、イベントグッズも発売しまーす！
Furthermore, event goods will also be on sale!
ストラップめっちゃいい！「迷宮なラビリンス」グッズ、今までなかったからね。
The straps are great! We didn't have any "Dramatic Labyrinth" goods until now.
イベントやグッズ情報について詳しくは特設サイト、ホロライブ公式Xの告知をご覧ください。
For more details on the event and goods, check the special site or the official hololive X account.
ぜひ、皆さん来てくださいねー！
Everyone, please come and join us!
続いてはクロたんお知らせ、お願いしまーす。
Next is Chloe-tan's announcement. Please go ahead!
はい！なんかめちゃくちゃスペシャルな内容になってるそうなので、皆さん驚いてください！
Yes! I hear it's going to be something very special, so everyone, prepare to be surprised!
驚けー！わー！
Be surprised! Whoa!
12月31日大晦日に、なんと地上波とホロライブ公式YouTubeチャンネルで、我らholoXがメインのスペシャルショートアニメが放送されます！
On New Year's Eve, December 31st, a special short anime featuring us, holoX, will air on TV and the official hololive YouTube channel!
おおー！
Ooooh!
めちゃめちゃ熱い展開！詳しい情報は、
Extremely hot developments! For more details,
X、旧Twitterからの情報を待っていてください。乞うご期待！
please wait for info on X (Twitter). Stay tuned!
ということで、次のお知らせはいろはちゃん！
And so, the next announcement is from Iroha-chan!
はい！じゃあですね、風真からお知らせさせていただきま、たたたたきます！
Yes! Well then, I will make an announcement from Kazama, a-a-a-announcement!
我ら holoX と、ホロプラスの連動プレゼントキャンペーンがスタートするでござる！
A holoPlus collaborative giveaway campaign for us, holoX, is starting!
皆様、ホロプラスは使ってくれていますか？
Everyone, are you using holoPlus?
使ってるよー！イエーイ！
We are! Yay!
合計13名に、hololive friends with u や、アクリルスタンドなど、
A total of 13 people will win holoX goods, such as 'hololive friends with u' plushies,
holoX グッズが当たりまーす！
acrylic stands, and more!
おー！
Oh!
応募期間は12月2日から来年の1月9日まで。
The application period is from December 2nd to January 9th of next year.
詳しい応募方法は、ホロプラスでご確認ください。
Please check holoPlus for detailed application instructions.
ホロプラスには「マイ推し」機能というのがあるので、
holoPlus has a 'My Oshi' feature,
ぜひ holoX をマイ推しに追加してほしいでござる！
so please add holoX to your 'My Oshi' list!
え、5個もらえるんだ、すごいね。
Wait, you get five of them? That's amazing.
すごいでござるな、飾ってござる、ゆっぴーだね、ホロプラス言えたね...
It's amazing, isn't it? Decorate them... you said 'holoPlus' correctly...
マジでちょっと情報が多すぎるんですけども...
Seriously, there's just too much information...
全部すごい情報なんで、みんなチェックしてね！
but it's all great info, so everyone please check it out!
これからも holoX 一丸全力で頑張っていくので、どうぞよろしくお願いします！
holoX will continue to work together and give it our all, so please look forward to us!
よろしくお願いします！
Please look forward to us!
おしらせもしたし...最後はライブで締め括りだわ！いくぞー！
Announcements are done... finally, let's wrap it up with a live performance! Let's go!
いくぞー！イエーイ！
Let's go! Yay!
La La PaTa Pa La La PaTa...
迷宮なラビリンス
A puzzling labyrinth
招かれた招待状
An invitation received
秘密で一時の異次元マンション
A secret temporary extra-dimensional mansion
ガタガタガタ 物音に
Gata-gata-gata... at the noise
No Pain, No Gain, Achi!
狙い澄ますホークアイ
Sharp-aimed Hawk-eye
迫る咆哮はウォークライ
The approaching roar is a War Cry
報酬条に突破口も
Breakthrough on the reward terms
走馬灯
A revolving lantern
Xに虜にされていくわ
Becoming captivated by X
かっこいいでござる！
How cool!
不条理な見学ツアー
An absurd tour
ドアからドアへ遊泳を
Swimming from door to door
さぁカスゴヤより今日は
Now, from the Kasugoya today
響け笑い声
Let the laughter ring out
La La PaTa Pa La La PaTa...
独り占め 本気？
Monopolizing? Seriously?
力こそパワー
Might is power
素敵な迷宮 ラビリンス
A wonderful maze, a labyrinth
並び立つシルエット
Silhouettes standing side-by-side
狂騒で切断Wi-Fi
Severed Wi-Fi by the frenzy
これマジで最強ルームだけど
This really is the strongest room, but...
刀の回転は普通に 危ない
The blade's rotation is normally dangerous
ワンショット ワンキル
One shot, one kill
虚実を踊るマリオネット
A marionette dancing between truth and lies
落ちる星は何処へ
Where do the falling stars go?
場外は眼中にない
The outside is not in sight
乱入は落雷 あかんくない？
Intrusion is a thunderbolt, isn't it bad?
Xに虜にされていく
Captivated by X
迷える子羊たち
The lost lambs
お砂糖スパイス それとピンクなものいっぱいで
Sugar, spice, and lots of pink things
ハイになれるドリンクできたよー！
A drink that makes you high is ready!
ロックで飲んでくださいね holoX だけに
Please drink it on the rocks... just like holoX!
さぁさ皆様のむでござる！
Now, everyone, let's drink!
お前が飲むんかい！
You're the one drinking?!
じゃあとりあえず 乾杯！
Well then, for now, cheers!
鏡の回廊から
From the mirror corridor
大幅な警報
A major alarm
塗り替えられる状況
An overwritten situation
見果てぬ笑い声
Unending laughter
お前たちもな！
You guys too!
La La PaTa Pa La La PaTa...
集え 5人のもと
Gather under the five of us
肩組んで 声をたからかに
Arms around shoulders, voices raised loud
La PaTa La La PaTa
エデンの
Eden's...
海を越えるため
...ocean to cross.
つまり本気
In other words, being serious
不屈が痛い
and indomitable is painful.
トキメかない級の
A level of heart-pounding...
スーパーフューチャーパーティーラビリンス
...super future party labyrinth!
バイ！
Bye!
うっ、何だこれ！？
Whoa, what is this!?
何だこれ！？
What is this!?
こよりが作りましたー！
Koyori made this!
おぉー！ すごーい！ 博士ー！
Ooh! Amazing! Doctor!
ねぇ、かっこいい！ でもこれ何？ 何？
Hey, it looks cool! But what is it? What is it?
ねぇねぇねぇ、これ何？ どうするの、これ？
Hey, hey, hey, what is it? What do we do with this?
ねぇ、これ爆発するの？ これ。
Hey, is this going to explode?
えー、いいから押してよ。
Come on, just press it.
待って、でもさ、何でいろはがそっち側に立ってるの？
Wait, but why is Iroha standing over there?
本当だよ、いろはも押せよ！
True, you press it too, Iroha!
やだぁー、いろはも押せー！
No way! Iroha, you press it too!
いいじゃん、これ、押してみなよ。
It's fine, just try pressing it.
いや、本当に… よいしょ。 お願いします。
No, really... there we go. Please go ahead.
こういうのはさ、人殺しだからな、本当に。
This kind of thing is murder, seriously.
そういうのさ、人殺しだと思ってんの！？
You think of this as murder!?
これが圧力だ！
This is pressure!
お前らを信じて…
Believing in you guys...
お前ら巻き込んでやるからな！
I'm dragging you all with me!
嫌だー！
Nooo!
ふざけんな！ こういうのやだー！
Don't mess with me! I hate this kind of thing!
うん、どれ、も、れ、とっ！
One, two, three, go!
うわぁー！ 綺麗ー！
Whoa! It's beautiful!
わぁ、すごーい！ 地球だー！
Wow, amazing! It's Earth!
え、宇宙！？ 本当に！？
Wait, space!? For real!?
あ、ベガの隣！
Ah, next to Vega!
どれどれ、ベガの隣？
Where, where? Next to Vega?
あれだ、あれあれ。
That's it, that one.
すごーい、宇宙まで来れたんだねー！
Amazing, we actually made it to space!
え、これもこよりが？
Wait, Koyori did this too?
そうだよ！ 宇宙ロケットを開発しました！
That's right! I developed a space rocket!
すごーい！ 本物のロケット！
Amazing! A real rocket!
すごすぎるー！ 発明家だー！
Too amazing! You're an inventor!
採用してよかったー！
I'm glad I hired you!
待って、発明家だと思ってたからね、もともとね。
Wait, I already thought she was an inventor.
かっこいい仕事だねー。
That's a cool job.
いつもいいもの作ってるでしょうが！
I'm always making good things, you know!
本当にちゃんと研究してたんだね。
You really were researching properly.
予算大丈夫かな？ 失敗したけど。
Is the budget okay? Even though it failed.
あ、心配しないで、大丈夫大丈夫。
Ah, don't worry, it's fine, it's fine.
これ、予算なくなる？
Will the budget run out with this?
あ、もともとないから大丈夫、大丈夫。
Ah, it wasn't there to begin with, so it's fine!
ひどいこと言ってるよー！ 博士に。
You're saying something terrible to the Doctor!
え、でも我々もついに宇宙進出ってことですよね！
Wait, but we've finally expanded into space!
あぁ、そうだね。
Ah, that's right.
よし！
Alright!
え、じゃあ全世界に向けて、我々の新曲を披露するぞ！
Wait, then we'll perform our new song for the whole world!
よっしゃー！
Alright!
いくぞー！
Here we go!
せーの！
Ready, set...
饗宴ソリダリティ
Festive Solidarity
～SHAKE★NABE～！
~SHAKE★NABE~!
闇！ Yummy！ 鍋会！
Dark! Yummy! Hot pot party!
Darkness！ Darkness！
Darkness! Darkness!
宴会 High！ High！
Party High! High!
闇！ Yummy！ 鍋会！
Dark! Yummy! Hot pot party!
征服！ 征服！
Conquest! Conquest!
宴会 High！ High！
Party High! High!
刮目せよー！
Behold!
暗黒の饗宴が今
The dark banquet now...
始まりを告げん！
...signals the beginning!
準備はいいでござるか？
Are you ready?
禁断の蓋を、解き放て！
Unleash the forbidden lid!
迷いの迷宮に 迷い込んだ子らよ
Children who have wandered into the labyrinth of confusion
ようこそ、今宵の饗宴へーーー
Welcome to tonight's banquet!
無礼講じゃんじゃん！
Let's party without restraint!
エンジョイな饗宴会
An enjoyable festive banquet
確信犯に 着火オーライ
Igniting the culprit, all right
夜なべ（土なべ）で煮込んだ
Stewed all night (in an earthen pot)
オ・タ・ノ・シ・ミ
L-o-o-k forward to it!
本気！～元デリシャスだった具材～
Serious! ~The ingredients that used to be delicious~
おーまーがー 禍々しいオーラやなぁ
Oh my god, what an ominous aura
ハチャメチャだって 5人よれば文殊の知恵
Even if it's messy, five people together have wisdom.
恋の出汁…ダバダバ
The broth of love... pouring out
苦汁も 我らの
Even the bitterness, within our...
受柱に おさめて
...receptacle, we'll contain it.
い・た・だ・き・まーす！（ハイ！）
Let's eat! (Hi!)
ジェケ★鍋イベー！ (ふー！)
Shake nabe, baby! (Whoo!)
C'mon！ エビ・バディバディ♪って
C'mon! Every-body-body ♪
とびっきり 大騒ぎしちゃえ！
Let's make an extraordinary fuss!
ぐっつぐつの ミラクルをつついて
Poking at the bubbling miracle
楽しんだもんが勝ち！おっおー！
The one who enjoys it wins! Oh-oh!
Check It！ 鍋 Event！ (ふー！)
Check it! Hot pot event! (Whoo!)
がっしょい Gotcha！ ましえまじえっ！？
Gasshoi Gotcha! More and more!?
ミクスチャー？ なんでもありあり？？
Mixture? Anything goes??
あつあつの スマイルを頬張って
Stuff your face with hot smiles
世界征服しよー！ おっおー！
Let's conquer the world! Oh-oh!
乙女に 必要な心得！
The mindset needed for a maiden!
一、箸を忘れない
One, don't forget the chopsticks!
二、恐れずに食べる
Two, eat without fear!
三、楽しむことだー！
Three, just enjoy it!
Yes My Dark!!!!
飢えた皆様の 安心安全を守る
Protecting the safety and security of you hungry people
この一刀旋風の如く 食材を刻む
Carving ingredients like a whirlwind with this blade
はーい！吾輩、食べる担当ー！
Yes! I'm in charge of eating!
毒でも 食べやすい大きさに
Making even poison an easy-to-eat size
シャキン！シャキン！シャキン！
Shakin! Shakin! Shakin!
お任せあれでござるー！
Leave it to me!
Dollar Dollar 鷹の目 (アイ)
Dollar Dollar hawk's eye
即・酒肴 低予算レシピ
Quick snacks, low-budget recipe
不安も不運も 闇に消してしまおう
Let's erase anxiety and bad luck into the darkness
グラグラ 煮え滾る
Bubbling and boiling
アク取り、お掃除、合法！
scum removal, cleaning, legal!
バイハーイ しちゃおな？
Shall we say bye-bye?
組織の力 (チカラ) を 召し上がれ！
Feast on the power of the organization!
ジェケ★鍋イベー！ (ふー！)
Shake nabe, baby! (Whoo!)
Get you！ いっちょ パヤパヤって
Get you! One more payapaya
やみつき！？ 凸撃！マシマシ！
Addictive!? Charging in, more and more!
はっちゃめちゃな スペシャルでもてなす
Treating you with a messy special
おかわりは どうですかー？ おっおー！
How about seconds? Oh-oh!
饗宴会 盛り上がってますかー？
Are you excited for the banquet party?
はーい！
Yes!
Don-dan-dan-dan-dan
実は、こっそり仕掛けをほどこしました！
Actually, I secretly set something up!
そろそろ効いてきたかなあ？
Is it starting to take effect yet?
じゃあ入れた具材を順番に言ってみよー
Now, let's say the ingredients we put in, one by one!
ナスーー！
Eggplant!
イカラーー！
Squid!
辛ーー！！
Spicy!!
か、かっこいー！吾輩もやるー！！
W-Wow, so cool! I'll do it too!!
どやぁ！大成功！
Tada! A huge success!
今度はみんなで、いくよー！
This time, all together, let's go!
ナスーー！！
Eggplant!!
イカラーー！！
Squid!!
辛ーー！！
Spicy!!
マヨーー！！
Mayo!!
からあげーー！！
Fried chicken!!
オムライスーー！！
Omelet rice!!
ハンバーグーー！！
Hamburger steak!!
なんで吾輩だけちがうんだよぉぉぉぉ！！
Why am I the only one who's different?!!
我らの集大成(キズナ)を示した逸品！
A masterpiece showing the culmination of our bonds!
「holoXなべ」が完成☆
The "holoX Nabe" is complete☆
笑顔で囲めば 心がひとつとなる
When we gather with smiles, our hearts become one.
これぞこそが真の仲間です (ハイ！)
This right here is what true comrades are! (Hi!)
SHAKE★NABE Event! ハッピーラッキー×ソリダリティ
SHAKE★NABE Event! Happy Lucky x Solidarity
ひとりじゃ 征服できないの！
I can't conquer it alone!
わっくわくの スマイルを届けて
Delivering a thrilling smile
この星を喰べたいんだ！おっおー！
I want to eat this planet! Oh-oh!
Check It！鍋 Event！(ふー！) わっちゃわちゃ ごちゃ混ぜで♪
Check It! Nabe Event! (Fu-!) All mixed up in a chaotic mess♪
ぷちょへんざっ みんなでJoin Join
Put your hands up! Everyone, join join!
あっちあっちの バイブスであふれた
Overflowing with piping hot vibes
世界征服 不可能じゃないわ！
World conquest is not impossible!
せーの！で決めポーズ！おっおー！
One, two! Strike a pose! Oh-oh!
闇！鍋会！Yummy！鍋会！
Dark! Nabe party! Yummy! Nabe party!
Darkness！Darkness！宴会High！High！
Darkness! Darkness! Banquet High! High!
Yummy！鍋会！Yummy！鍋会！
Yummy! Nabe party! Yummy! Nabe party!
征服！征服！宴会 満腹！
Conquest! Conquest! Full from the banquet!
(Wah wah wah wah, Wah wah wah)
あーーー！！
Aaaaah!!
わぁぁぁ！！
Waaaaah!!
あれを見ろ！
Look at that!
うわぁ！
Whoa!
何？
What?
ライブかいじょー
Live Venue
え、おい！ あ、待てよこれ！
Eh, hey! Wait, look at this!
何て事だよ！
What the heck!
我々、宇宙進出じゃなかったのか！？
Weren't we supposed to be expanding into space!?
いや、予算の限界です。
No, it's the budget limit.
えー！ 待てよ！ 予算使いすぎちゃったの！？ 今更！？
Eh! Wait! You spent too much budget!? Now of all times!?
予算がないから悪いんだよ！
It's because there's no budget!
何で予算ないんだよ！ふざけんなよ！
Why is there no budget!? Don't mess with me!
予算で遊んでる奴がいるからだよ！ 予算返せよ！
It's because someone's playing around with the budget! Give it back!
吾輩の見せ場じゃなかったのかよぉぉぉぉ！！嫌だーー！！
Wasn't this supposed to be my big moment?!! Nooo!!
holoX 2周年だえ!!!!!
It's holoX 2nd anniversary!!!!!
holoX 2周年 ありがとう!!
holoX 2nd anniversary, thank you!!
holoX 2周年 ありがとう! Thank you
holoX 2nd anniversary, thank you! Thank you
holoX 2周年だえ!!!!!
It's holoX 2nd anniversary!!!!!
祝☆holoX 2周年~!!
Celebration☆holoX 2nd anniversary~!!
嗚呼 誰が僕にじゃんじゃん！
Ah, who's pouring for me, more and more!
エンジェの分も 注文オーライ
Ordering for Ange too, all right
夜なべで煮込んだ (一瞬だけにゃんこ☆コン)
Stewed overnight (Meow for just a moment☆con)
O・TA・NO・SHI・MI
E-N-J-O-Y-M-E-N-T
集中~！完デリシャスだった具材
Concentration~! The ingredients were completely delicious
おーまいがー 腹へいオーライ
Oh my god, hungry, all right
めちゃめちゃだって 五人よれば 文殊の知恵
Even if it's a mess, five heads are better than one
いい出汁 ダダダダ ダシも笑えば
Good broth, da-da-da-da, even the broth smiles
シチュ中に収めて いただきます！
Keep it in the stew, let's eat!
ハイ！
Hi!
このあとMV公開！
MV public release after this!
近日公開 秘密結社holoX 「響宴ソリダリティ~SHAKE★NABE~」 リリース記念ボイス
Coming Soon: Secret Society holoX "Kyoushin Solidarity ~SHAKE★NABE~" Release Commemoration Voice
この後 ホロライブ公式チャンネルでMV公開!!
MV public release on the Hololive official channel after this!!
爆食い リンクディリティ (SHAKEY MODE)
この後 ホロライブ公式チャンネルでMV公開！
Binge-Eating Link-derity (SHAKEY MODE)
MV release on the Hololive official channel after this!